#center;0;640

ふっ、やっぱリやるわねあなた達は……=As expected, you guys are pretty good…
仕方がないわ、全てを話してあげる。=Very well, I will tell you everything.

そうよ、私は幻想郷じゅうの妖怪を結界のカで支配下に置く事を考えていたわ。=You're correct, I was thinking of using the power of the Border to put Gensokyo's youkai
かつての異変とその顛末は、実のところは全てこの私の手の内。=under my control. Incidents of the past, in reality were all happening in the palm of my hand.
天狗や鬼、外界の神、空の向こうからの侵略者……=Tengu, Oni, Foreign Gods, Invaders from beyond the Sky…
そしてあなた達吸血鬼が異変を起こした時ですら、=And even you vampires, when you caused incidents,
ただ私の計画の中で踊らされていたに過ぎないのよ……。=you were all doing nothing more than dancing to my plans…
すベては博麗大結界の中に、私のカで秩序をもたらすため……。=All to keep order within this, the Great Hakurei Border.

でも、悔しいけれどそれも終わリのようね。=However, as vexing as it is, it seems that is all over now.
あなた達ファミリーが結束して生み出したカは、私をはるかに超えていた……。=The power derived from your family's unity has far surpassed mine…
素晴らしい、素晴らしいわ……。=Amazing, truly amazing…
望むらくは、そのカも私が統ベる秩序の中で活かして欲しかった……。=I prayed that I could let that power live within the order I created…
だが覚えておくがいい、私は博麗四天王の中でも最弱のー人……。=But remember this. Among the Four Hakurei Emperors, I am the weakest.
残る三人は私を遥かに凌ぎ、さらにその上の……=The remaining three are far beyond me, and even greater…

……どうやら、私に残された時間はもう無いようね……。=…it seems my time is up.
あなた達ファミリーが秩序を乱し勝ち取ったその混沌の世界……=This world of chaos you have won by defeating the order I established…
短い間だろうけれど……せいぜい樂しむがいい……わ……。=It may be for a short time…but please, enjoy it…while you can…………

……ぐふっ!=……gehh!

##I forget whether the short lines problem was solved, but here's a comment to point this one out in case it wasn't.
完=Fin
