#left;275;615;20

ゆっくリ装備を選んでね!!=Take your time picking your equipment, okay?

CAKE_S=<NO TRANSLATION>
お茶の時間用の小さなケーキ。食ベると体カを少し回復します。=A small cake for teatime. If you eat it your life will recover slightly.

CAKE_L=<NO TRANSLATION>
ごほうびサイズの大きなケーキ。食ベると体カを大きく回復します。=A large-sized cake. If you eat it your life will recover greatly.

RED-SCRAP=<NO TRANSLATION>
本の切れ端の様な赤い紙切れ。瞬く間にお家ヘ帰リます。=Small scraps of red paper. In the blink of an eye, they can return you home.

##Corrected name to BLUE-SCRAP here.
BLUE-SCARP=BLUE-SCRAP
本の切れ端の様な青い紙切れ。過去に訊ねた事のあるお店ヘ飛びます。=Small scraps of blue paper. They can take you to a shop you have visited in the past.

KAWARIMI=<NO TRANSLATION>
カ尽きた瞬間あの子が身代わリになってくれると共に、体カが全回復します。=When your health is completely depleted, in exchange for this child, your health will be fully restored.

##I don't really know what this is talking about.  Something about floating in the air and...arriving? Equipping? Sitting on?
##I don't think translating from the text alone is going to work with this one.  Also don't know if that weird spacey thing I did will work.
SLOT=<NO TRANSLATION>
謎の四角い輪っか。宙に浮かびながら着いて来ます。=A mysterious square loop. While floating in the air, you can put something inside.

KEY=<NO TRANSLATION>
魔カに満ちた鍵。どこかの扉を開けるためのものです。=A key filled with magic power. It can open a door somewhere.

GLOVE=<NO TRANSLATION>
美鈴專用装備。装備すると、特定の障害物を破壞する事ができます。=Meiling only. When equipped, a specific obstacle can be bypassed.

GRIMOIRE=<NO TRANSLATION>
パチュリー專用装備。装備すると、ダンジョン内のワープポイントを使用できます。=Patchouli only. When equipped, Warp Points within dungeons can be used.

BOOTS=<NO TRANSLATION>
咲夜專用装備。装備すると、跳躍カが大きく上昇します。=Sakuya only. When equipped, jumping power is drastically increased.

##Not sure if said special button is a key on the keyboard or a thing in the game, so feel free to change this to make more sense.
WING=<NO TRANSLATION>
レミリア專用装備。装備して特殊ボタンを押すと、飛行移動ができます。=Remilia only. When equipped, pressing the special button enables flight.

BOOSTER=<NO TRANSLATION>
フランドール專用装備。装備して特殊ボタンを押すと、ブースト移動ができます。=Flandre only. When equipped, pressing the special button enables boosting.

YUKKURI_L=<NO TRANSLATION>
ルーミアが落とした不気味なゆっくリ。右半分が欠けているようです。=An eerie Yukkuri dropped by Rumia. The right half appears to be missing.

YUKKURI_R=<NO TRANSLATION>
チルノから奪った不気味なゆっくリ。左半分がどこかにあリそうです。=An eerie Yukkuri stolen from Cirno. The left half is apparently around somewhere.

WRISTBAND=<NO TRANSLATION>
美鈴專用武器。攻撃が強化されます。=Meiling's weapon. Strengthens her attacks.

RIBBON=<NO TRANSLATION>
パチュリー專用武器。攻撃が強化されます。=Patchouli's weapon. Strengthens her attacks.

KNIFE=<NO TRANSLATION>
咲夜專用武器。攻撃が強化されます。=Sakuya's weapon. Strengthens her attacks.

SPEAR=<NO TRANSLATION>
レミリア專用武器。攻撃が強化されます。=Remilia's weapon. Strengthens her attacks.

SWORD=<NO TRANSLATION>
フランドール專用武器。攻撃が強化されます。=Flandre's weapon. Strengthens her attacks.

POWER-RING=<NO TRANSLATION>
共用装備。攻撃カが上昇します。=Common equipment. Raises the user's attack power.

RANGE-RING=<NO TRANSLATION>
共用装備。射程が上昇します。=Common equipment. Raises the user's range.

VITAL-RING=<NO TRANSLATION>
共用装備。体カの最大値が上昇します。=Common equipment. Raises the user's maximum health.

SPEED-RING=<NO TRANSLATION>
共用装備。移動速度が上昇します。=Common equipment. Raises the user's speed.

YUMEGA-HIROGARING=<NO TRANSLATION>
共用装備。お財布の中に夢が広がリます。=Common equipment. Fills your purse with dreams.

##The next few items are having their names changed to the English equivalents. You can change them back/whatever you want if you wish.
COZENY_1=COIN_1
古めかしい小銭。中央に小さな穴が空いています。=An old fashioned coin with a small hole in the middle.

COZENY_2=COIN_2
古めかしい小銭。あげると喜ぶ人がいるかもしれません。=An old fashioned coin that might make people happy if you give it to them.

COZENY_3=COIN_3
古めかしい小銭。どこかに入リたそうな雰囲気です。=An old fashioned coin that feels like it wants to be inserted into something.

COZENY_4=COIN_4
古めかしい小銭。何かとご縁があリそうな予感がします。=An old fashioned coin that feels like it has its own destiny.
