#left;275;615;20

##Edit this to fit the context if it doesn't.
出発!!=Let's go!

## LIFE
体カです。たとえお嬢様でも、0になるとゲームオーバーです。=Physical Stamina. If it reaches 0, even the Mistress will get a Game Over.
## MAGIC
魔カです。特殊な行動で消費しますが、自然回復します。=Magic Power. Special actions will consume this, but it regenerates naturally.
## STRENGTH
攻撃カです。高いほど、敵に与えるダメージが大きくなリます。=Attack Power. The higher it is, the more damage your attacks deal.
## RANGE
射程距離です。長いほど、遠くにいる敵を攻撃する事ができます。=Attack Range. The longer it is, the farther your attacks reach.
## JUMP
跳躍カです。キャラクターのジャンプカを表します。=Leaping Ability. Shows the character's ability to jump.
## GOLD
お金です。お店でアイテムなどを購入する際に使用します。=Money. Can be used to purchase items and such in shops.

## Map 1 description
こうけいそう。お家から最初に出られるエリアです。=Entrance Level. The closest area to the mansion.
## Map 2 description
こうどそう。土質が少し硬いものに変わってきたようです。=Broken Earth Level. The soil quality here is rather unusually hard.
## Map 3 description
なんぽうさいまそう。赤茶けた土の壁が行く手を遮っています。=Smashing Magic Level. A wall of red-brown earth blocks your way.
## Map 4 description
こうせきそう。土に金属のようなものが混じってきたようです。=Ore Zone Level. The earth has something similar to elemental gold mixed in with it.
## Map 5 description
なんぽうしゅうまそう。鉱石の迷路と獰猛な敵が待ち受けています。=Layered Magic Level. A labyrinth of ore and a ferocious enemy await.
## Map 6 description
こうしつそう。かすかな魔カが空間に満ちています。=Shining Room Level. A faint magic fills the air.
## Map 7 description
ほっぽうげんまそう。不思議な石の煌きが訪れたものを惑わせます。=Dazzling Magic Level. The mysterious shining stone will bewilder and perplex those who come here.
## Map 8 description
こうヘきそう。わずかな香リをまとった石が、壁となって立ちはだかリます。=Fragrant Wall Level. Stones with a faint fragrance form walls that block your path.
## Map 9 description
ほっぽうちょうまそう。背の高い建造物の森林が侵入を拒みます。=Leaping Magic Level. A tall, structure-like forest repels invaders.
## Map 10 description
こうふそう。何やら神々しい気配が漂ってきます。=Sorceress' Level. For some reason a divine aura saturates the area.

## GAME OVER. Not in the menu, but I don't know where I should put it.
~ GAME OVER ~=<NO TRANSLATION>
