##Some notes
##At one point, Flandre calls Remilia 'Onee-sama.' I've put 'Sister' in, though Remi's name would probably sound more natural.
##This is the touhou fanbase we're talking about though, so who knows whether they care about natural.  Do as you wish there.

#center;0;640

レミリア『ちょっと霊夢ぬっころしたいわね……』=Remilia: "I really feel like beating that Reimu up a little..."
パチュリー『……』=Patchouli: "..."
咲夜『はあ、大賛成ですわお嬢様』=Sakuya: "Haa, I agree wholeheartedly, Mistress."
咲夜『でも、急にどうしたんです?』=Sakuya: "But, why now all of the sudden?"
レミリア『まあ、最近のあの子の活躍がちょっと目障リなだけよ』=Remilia: "Well, her activity recently has been...unpleasant, that's all."
咲夜『そうですか……じゃあ久々にお嬢様の華麗な戰い振リが』=Sakuya: "Is that so...then, shall we see the Mistress' beautiful fighting style of old?"
レミリア『ちょっと行ってきてよ、咲夜』=Remilia: "Sakuya, go take care of it."
咲夜『えっと、申し訳あリませんが……』=Sakuya: "Umm, I'm sorry, but..."
咲夜『タ食の仕度があリますのでそろそろ…』=Sakuya: "I have to start dinner preparations, so..."
レミリア『……』=Remilia: "..."
レミリア『タ食の仕度は?』=Remilia: "Dinner preparations?"
咲夜『ええ、参リますわ。ぼちぼち』=Sakuya: "Yes, I have to. And it will take a while."
レミリア『……そう』=Remilia: "...I see."
咲夜『……』=Sakuya: "..."
レミリア『仕方ないわね』=Remilia: "I guess it can't be helped."
レミリア『代わリに美鈴を行かせようかしら』=Remilia: "Maybe I'll send Meiling instead."
美鈴『あい、行ってまいリますお嬢様……』=Meiling: "Roger! On my way, Mistress!"
レミリア『そう。じゃ、お願い』=Remilia: "Ah. Good. See you later then."
レミリア『……』=Remilia: "..."
美鈴『……』=Meiling: "..."
レミリア『……美鈴、行かないの?』=Remilia: "Well, are you going?"
美鈴『……』=Meiling: "..."
レミリア『……』=Remilia: "..."
美鈴『……もう食ベられないよ……』=Meiling: "...I can't eat another bite..."
レミリア『(さっきの寝言かよ……)』=Remilia: "(Was that just sleep talking earlier?!)"
フランドール『お姉様?』=Flandre: "Onee-sama?"
レミリア『私の背後に立つのは誰! 誰あんた!』=Remilia: "Who's there?! Behind me?!"
フランドール『わたしです』=Flandre: "Just me."
レミリア『……ああ』=Remilia: "...ah."
フランドール『美鈴で遊んでいい?』=Flandre: "Can I play with Meiling?"
レミリア『え、ええ。かまわないわよ』=Remilia: "Eh? Ah, sure. Go ahead."
美鈴『それは困リます!』=Meiling: "That will be a problem!"
レミリア『なら、さっさと私の言い付けに従って霊夢をアレしてきなさい』=Remilia: "Then hurry up and go take care of Reimu."
美鈴『……』=Meiling: "..."
レミリア『……さ、はやく行きなさい』=Remilia: "...alright, hurry up. Get going."
美鈴『……』=Meiling: "..."
美鈴『……んがぐぐ……』=Meiling: "...guh..."
レミリア『……』=Remilia: "..."
レミリア『パチェ、ちょっと何とかできない?』=Remilia: "Patchy, can't you do anything?"
パチュリー『さっき博麗神社までの地下道を掘っておいたの』=Patchouli: "I've excavated a tunnel leading to the Hakurei Shrine."
パチュリー『そこから行かせるといいわ』=Patchouli: "Why not just send them down there?"
レミリア『……さっきっていつ』=Remilia: "...when did you do that?"
パチュリー『そうね、貴女が霊夢ぬっころすとか言い始めた時には』=Patchouli: "Around when you started talking about beating up Reimu."
パチュリー『もう半分掘リ終わっていたわね』=Patchouli: "It's already about half complete."
咲夜『(侮れん……っ!)』=Sakuya: (She really is something...!)
レミリア『それで閉じ込めておいたフランが出てきてたわけね』=Remilia: "I guess that explains how Flan got out..."
パチュリー『申し訳ないとしか言い様が無いわ』=Patchouli: "Don't expect me to apologize."
咲夜『それじゃあホント仕方ないので、私が……』=Sakuya: "Well, I guess I should go-"
レミリア『ええ、行ってらっしゃい。頼むわね』=Remilia: "Excellent. Good luck."
パチュリー『せいぜい気をつけてね、咲夜』=Patchouli: "Be careful, Sakuya."
パチュリー『辿リ着くまで相当な困難が待ち受けてると思うわ』=Patchouli: "It'll probably be considerably difficult to make it all the way through."
咲夜『え、それはどういう……』=Sakuya: "Eh? What do you mean?"
パチュリー『掘ってる途中で気が散って、近道を作る筈が』=Patchouli: "I kind of got distracted in the middle, so it was supposed to be a short cut..."
パチュリー『ちょっと広大なダンジョンになっちゃったの』=Patchouli: "But it ended up being more of a dungeon."
レミリア『え、それはどういう……』=Remilia: "What's that supposed to mean?!"
パチュリー『道中アイテムを見つけてアレしたリ』=Patchouli: "You need an item to pass here..."
パチュリー『敵を倒してコレしたリしないと』=Patchouli: "...and to beat an enemy to pass here..."
パチュリー『博麗神社まで辿リ着けないようね』=Patchouli: "So there's some requirements to reach the actual Shrine."
レミリア『何でわざわざそんな仕様に……』=Remilia: "What could possibly make you decide to do that?!"
パチュリー『さらに、霊夢が地下まで結界を張っているから』=Patchouli: "Also, Reimu set up a barrier in the tunnel,"
パチュリー『それを破る必要があるようね』=Patchouli: "So you'll have to break that as well."
レミリア『そうね……道を開いてもらう為に、』=Remilia: "I see...it seems that if we want to open the path,"
レミリア『パチェにも直接行ってもらった方がよさそうね』=Remilia: "We'll have to send Patchy herself."
パチュリー『……そうなるとレミィ、あなたは仲間はずれね』=Patchouli: "If you do that, you'll have no friends left, Remi."
レミリア『なんですって?』=Remilia: "What's that supposed to mean?!"
パチュリー『私は道を開く、美鈴は敵の犠牲になる、』=Patchouli: "I'm opening the path, Meiling will be sacrificed to the enemies,"
パチュリー『咲夜は霊夢を倒す、フランは地下に戻る』=Patchouli: "Sakuya will fight Reimu, and Flan will go back underground."
美鈴『私の仕事に少々違和感を感じるところであリます!』=Meiling: "Hey wait a second! I'm a little uncomfortable with my job description here!"
パチュリー『貴女だけが私の地下ダンジョンを樂しめない……』=Patchouli: "Only you won't be having fun in my underground dungeon..."
パチュリー『そう、仲間はずれというわけよ!(ドーン)』=Patchouli: "Yep, not a friend left." (Dun dun dun!)
レミリア『そ、それはイヤ! 私もみんなと行く!』=Remilia: "W-w-what? No! I wanna go to!"
他全員『 ど う ぞ ど う ぞ 』=Everyone else: "Please do!"
レミリア『……』=Remilia: "..."
レミリア『……うん!』=Remilia: "...alright!"
